Let's take our basic Egyptian Walk and travel in a circle with it.
So let's start with the footwork.
Right foot, left up on toe.
Left, right on toe.
Make sure you're putting pressure on that ball of that foot.
So it's going to be; step, touch, so arms just out, palms down facing away from the body.
We call this a low ibis arm.
Step, touch, step and touch.
And as you touch you're going to lift that hip.
Step, touch.
Good.
So we're going to travel to the right, so we're going to step out with the right foot and feet together, step back with the left foot, feet together, step, together, step, together.
So we're hitting the four corners of the room.
Let's try it again.
Ready and turn, step, together, step, hip, step, hip, step and hip.
Good.
Try the other direction, stepping left foot.
Left, hip, step, face the back, step, face the side and step, face forward.
Good.
You want to make sure that everytime you turn, that your knees line up in the same direction, so that our knees aren't going in two different directions.
You want to keep your body nice and align.